hi I'm Mike Morton vice president of
Microsoft Dynamics 365 business Central
today's rapidly involving landscape
employees are the Beating Heart of your
company they are your most valuable
asset to achieve your strategic goals if
you're a business Central partner
looking to expand your Workforce then we
are really excited to introduce to you
the res skill program res skill is the
product of a collaboration between
Microsoft and our development Partners
it cultivates a new Talent by recruiting
individuals with industry knowledge or
transferable skills goals into your
organization it includes product and
Professional Training it guides new
hires to become proficient in BC
professionals and all of this at an
affordable cost and with minimal risk to
partners partners worldwide have
embraced this program the feedback we've
received so far speaks for itself it
affirms its Effectiveness we're proud to
share the current retention rate of new
hires from the last 12 months is
99.2% and we are committed to nurturing
that Talent res skills training and
coaching approach enables new hires to
make contributions and billable customer
activities within just 8 to 12 weeks
after they on board recently I had the
chance to meet new consultants and
developers who were able to enter the
ecosystem thanks to the res skill
program their enthusiasm their passion
the Gratitude they showed me once again
just showed the value of investing in
new people they inspired me with their
ideas and their fresh learnings and
perspectives our Collective
responsibility to nurture the Next
Generation to drive Innovation to grow
and help build a brighter tomorrow
Microsoft is committed to investing in
BC Talent come and join us so we can
Bridge the talent Gap
[Music]